Shreyansh Kumar

shreyanshkumar058@gmail.com | +917878757744 www.shreyanshkr.com | shreyansh.kumar2020@vitbhopal.ac.in

EDUCATION

VIT BHOPAL UNIVERSITY, BHOPAL

(2020-2024) B.Tech Computer Science GPA-8

RNP PUBLIC SCHOOL, CHHAPRA, BIHAR

(2016-17) Matriculation & (2018-19) Intermediate

LINKS

Github: /ffshreyansh **Linkedin:** /shreyansh-kr **Twitter:** /shreyanshtwts

SKILLS

PROGRAMMING

- * HTML5 * CSS3 * Bootstrap5
- * Javascript * Node.Js
- * Express.Js * EJS * Flutter
- * Firebase * Static Websites
- * Dynamic Website.

Familiar Languages:

* Java * C++

DESIGN

- * Adobe Illustrator * Adobe Ps
- * Adobe Premiere Pro
- * Adobe After Effects

INTERESTS

- * Reading Non-Fiction Books
- * Content Creation * Learning about films & direction.

SUMMARY

I am a third-year computer science student and self-taught web developer with experience in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node.js, and Express.js. In addition to my technical skills, I also have experience in graphic design, with a strong foundation in converting designs from graphic to web. I am a proactive learner with a passion for building and designing intuitive, user-friendly websites.

EXPERIENCE

SUSHILAP | Front-end developer & Designer Sept 2021 - March 2021

- Developed and Designed static sushilap.com using front-end tech stacks i.e HTML, CSS & JS only
- Improved Web Designs of sunnydaycarers.co.au & aussieyouthcare.co.au
- Created Websites and Designs to get pitched infront of clients and companies

GOOGLE DSC | Creative Designer & Editor Jan 2021 - June 2021

- Designed hackDSC.tech
- Designed Promotional Content

XOOG.IN | Creative Designer & Editor April 2022 - July 2022

- Designed UI contents and Playstore Contents
- Designed Promotional Content

PROJECTS

PORTFOLIO WEBSITE * SUSHI LAP-WEBSITE * BLOGSITE

- Created a static site using HTML, BOOTSTRAP, CSS & JS.

DHARMA CHARIOT, COMMUNITY WEBSITE CLONE

- Blog Site for Youtube channel Dharma Chariot. Tech stacks used Bootstrap and Javascript to make the site static. Updates are with NodeJS and Express for the Dynamic site.

PASSPORT USER AUTH, DICTIONARY API SITE, ILJAVANECK PORTFOLIO CLONE

- Tech Stacks used HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, NodeJS, ExpressJS, EJS, MongoDB